Register of the S. I. Hayakawa papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Administrative/Legislative Files (Boxes 1-265)
  - Press tapes - audio (Box 233)
    - interview with New West magazine, 3/2/80
    - hearings re: Solar Commercialization Act (2 tapes), 3/3/80
    - interview: American Sovereignty Act, 3/11/80
    - floor statement re: American Sovereignty Protection Act, 3/19/80
    - Advisory Committee discussion re: agriculture/immigration and American Sovereignty Protection Act, 3/21/80
    - press conference and speech - JACL, 3/22/80
    - speech at Health Industry Manufacturers Association, Palm Springs, 3/29/80
    - interview with WRC TC, Washington, re: Iran, 4/1/80
    - Iran Express, 4/2/80
    - interview with Sacramento Union, 4/15/80
    - press conference re: Iran; press conference, California Office (2 tapes), 4/16/80
    - editorial response for KABC, 4/17/80
    - actuality, Big Sur, 5/5/80
    - National Republic Platform Hearing re: knowledge elite; actuality re: Bug Sur, 5/8/80
    - interview with KRON re: ride sharing, 5/16/80
    - interview with McLean magazine, 5/21/80
    - interview for Sunday Profile magazine of Valley News; interview with Orange County Register, 5/24/80
    - speech at Harbor Lawn Memorial Park, 5/26/80
    - statement on Secretary of State Muskie, 5/80
    - testimony at Select Commission on Refugees hearing, 6/9/80
    - interview for Radio Show re: small business, 10/2/80
    - interview for KCBS-SF re: Presidential Debates, 10/28/80
    - interview with Sacramento Union, 11/17/80
    - - Interview for radio re: foreign relations, 1980
  - Videotape "Hayakawa Today" (Box 234)
  - Press photos
  - Press photos (Box 235)
  - Photographs (Box 236)
    - SIH visits Lawrence Livermore Laboratory, 11/8/76
    - Stanislaus State College students, 1/2/77
    - 1/4/77
      - Swearing In with Senators Curtis and Thurmond
      - Casual photo
      - Danuma Doll Press Conference
      - Republican Conference
      - Swearing In
      - Swearing In with VP Rockefeller
      - Swearing In with SIH family
      - Dunuma Doll
    - 1/12/77
      - Mr. Blackistone, florist, for Heart Association
      - Tam-o-shanter
    - 1/3/77
      - Eugene Mannila, Alice Saathoff, friends
      - Dorothy Chagenovich, Naval Supply Woman of the Year
    - A. Philip Bray, winner, E. A. Lawrence Award for Energy, 1/14/77
    - Roger Mudd TV show, 1/16/77
    - 1/17/77
      - CA Youth Inaugural Delegation (Josh Wilson)
      - George Merrick, President Rockwell International Space Division
    - 1/19/77
      - Gerald Ford
      - President Carter State of the Union Address
      - Congressman Lagomarsino with Filmore HS students
    - Inaugural Ceremony for President Carter, 1/20/77
    - Peter Gottheiner, National Home Care Inc. of SF, 1/21/77
    - 1/26/77
      - SIH ID photo
      - Grant C. Pinney and Robert Murphy
    - 1/27/77
      - Donald and David Jackson, San Joaquin farmers
      - Stan Doyka
      - Scheduling Secretary Steve Vaccariello
      - SIH photos
      - Candid SIH office photos
    - Major John Vernon, Vietnam vet from Redwood City, CA, 2/1/77
    - US Senate Youth Program delegate Michael Miller, 2/2/77
    - 2/3/77
      - Ambassador Punch Coomanaswamy of Singapore
      - Presidential classroom delegates
    - Breakfast for CA Republican Delegation, 2/4/77
    - 2/8/77
      - Ralph Millikin, Pres. CA Med. Assn., Dr. Cohn, Chairman, Council; Al Pross, CA Med. Assn. and Dr. Joe Takamine, Chairman, Cal-Pac
      - Walgreen Drugs representatives
      - National School Board Association members
    - Presidential classroom delegates, 2/10/77
    - Asst. Secretary of State Dannell St. Claire after SIH delivers Washington Farewell Address, 2/21/77
    - Presidential classroom delegates, 2/24/77
    - Warren Christopher, nominee, Dept. Secretary of State, 2/25/77
    - Presidential classroom delegates, 3/3/77
    - National League of Cities Convention delegates, 3/7/77
    - 3/8/77
      - Science Service Award winner John Belleveau
      - Gene Prat and Elvira Orly
    - Sen. and Mr. Robert Brouse, Shaklee Corp., 3/16/77
    - 3/17/77
      - Stanford Sloan fellows
      - Congressman Fred Schwengel, Pres., Cap. Historical Society
    - 3/23/77
      - Teacher of the Year Mrs. Myrna Lenora Lee (2 photos)
    - 3/29/77
      - San Diego Chapter Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge
      - Boy of the Year CA finalists Richard Forslund, Frank Garduno, Director Charles Conley
      - John Komperds, Contra Costa County Dinner
    - Boy Scout Troop 39, Santa Venetia, CA; St. Mary's students, San Jose; Newport Harbor HS students; Whittier Union HS students, 4/5/77
    - 4/19/77
      - Hugh McDonald, Teamsters, S.D.; I.M. Ryam, President, REMCO
      - Dr. David Olch, Beverly Hills
    - Joint Session of Congress, 4/20/77
    - John Kunst family, 4/29/77
    - USC students Mike Mikasa, Chuck Wilcox, Mark Harris, 5/12/77 (Box 237)
    - 5/18/77
      - Mr. Arlo Sorenson, J. E. Greene, Sherry Hutchinson, Whittier Corp.
      - Prime Contractor of the Year Mr. Bernard Katz
    - Redwood Loggers Rally, 5/24/77
    - Intern Maureen Patty, 5/25/77
    - 5/26/77
      - Mr. and Mrs. James den Eykel and daughter Britt
      - Masar Tsuyama, Pres. CA First Bank, & Mrs. Mike Masaoka
      - H. A. Applegate, Exec. Director DECA & Becky Klub
    - Peter Shor, winner 6th USA math olympiad and parents, 6/7/77
    - Richard Keller, Atty., Board of Trustees, Ohlone College, 6/9/77
    - 6/10/77
      - Page David Tulanian
      - Marcella Whitmore of Arcadia, SIH worker
      - Spelling champions Melinda Lilly and Jane Labib
    - Brig. Gen. A. P. McMillan and Marines, 6/17/77
    - SIH and Laxalt staffers re: Lake Tahoe Project, 6/20/77
    - Congressman Pickle, Gold Pickle Award, 6/24/77
    - Senators Hayakawa, Chafee and Schweiker, 7/77
    - 7/15/77
      - Buck Fawcett, Fran. Simpson, CA Beef Cattle Feeders
      - Sunny Mojonnier, Pres. So. CA Nisei Farmers League
    - FFA members Mark Hoag and Gary Sauza, 7/22/77
    - School principals Patrick Baker, Rudi Medina, Dolores Luhns, Delores Parkers, 7/25/77
    - 7/29/77
      - Marion McDowell, staff
      - Interns Joel Curtis, John Spees, Betsy Graves, Tracy Morgan, Tammy Thompson, Jim Selth
      - Teachers Flo Anne Keith
      - Allene Zangene, staff
    - Former Congressman Roger Zion, 8/1/77
    - SIH in Ashville, NC, 9/11/77
    - Ruth Braley, Jan Hedlund, Michele Laxalt at Bloomingdale's for African Museum of Art, 9/17/77
    - Special Olympics, 9/19/77
    - CA Supervisors, 9/21/77
    - Bruce Jenner, Sandy O'Hara (staff), 10/14/77
    - Senator Humphrey, 10/25/77
    - David Harmer, 10/27/77
    - Hearings, 11/77
    - 11/3/77
      - Intern Dan Ichinaga
      - California women in agriculture
    - 12/6/77
      - SIH passport photo
      - Gene Prat passport photo
    - Intern Alyssa Popeil, Page Louise Ichinose, Scheduling Secretary Steve Vaccariello, 12/9/77
    - Deborah Graham, staff, 12/14/77
    - Mr. Herbert Turner, Assoc. Bldg. & Contractors, 1/20/78
    - 1/20/78
      - SIH in tam
      - California farmers
    - Apricot producers in California (Jack Hestilow, Ivan Bays, Ralph Watters, Lauren Campbell), 1/23/78
    - Alliance of Metal Working Industries, 1/24/78
    - Chicano "dropout" students, 1/25/78
    - CA Sheet Metal & Air Conditioning Contractors (w/Gene Prat and Dr. Backer), 1/30/78
    - Presidential classroom, 1/31/78
    - SIH speaking, 2/78
    - Senator Cranston w/Senate Youth Program Winners, 2/1/78
    - Francine Malone and IWY Group, 2/2/78
    - Mr. Kazarian, Dr. Merenda, Walter Clark & Assoc., 2/3/78
    - Assn. of Community Colleges, 2/6/78
    - 2/18/78
      - Gene Prat & Harry Kubo, San Joaquin Nisei Farmers League banquet
      - Assemblymen Carman, Perrino, Waters
      - Senator Stall, San Joaquin Nisei Farmers League banquet
    - Justin Dart, 2/21/78
    - 2/24/78
      - Dean Rider
      - Delphine Cannon and Mr. Cannon
    - 2/27/78
      - Eileen Hamm, June Duran, Ingelborg Pattee / McGraw-Hill
      - Members, Community Health Assn. (S. Sylvester Lee, Louis Garcia, Donald Fink, Harold Hambrich, Dorothy Reno, Geraldine Branch, Charles Debose, Gabriel Arce)
    - 2/28/78
      - Presidential classroom
      - Gene Prat, Harry Kubo
      - Mary Goedde, Yoshio Inadomi, Harry Kubo, Sam Minami
      - Randy Gruber, staff aide
      - San Minami
      - Yoshio Inadomi
      - Harry Kubo, President, Nisei Farmers League
      - Staff picture (listing enclosed)
    - 3/6/78 (Box 238)
      - Gene Prat & Councilman Lawrence Pegram of San Jose
      - Gene Prat and Ernie Cobine
    - Orange County Consortium of Cities w/Grace, Betty, Gene, 3/9/78
    - CA elected county officials, 3/13/78
    - Norma Gater/Morgan Vail, Lodi Unified School District, 3/22/78
    - 3/23/78
      - Caroline and Edie Thompson (intern)
      - Brock Spore, Dorothy Saunder, grandmother and grandson
    - Frank Laurie, Mrs. Jean Hill, 3/27/78
    - William L. Dick at D.C. reception, 4/4/78
    - San Diego Chamber of Commerce (John Murphy & Lee Grissom), 4/5/78
    - Freedom Foundation Essay Winners - Pacific Palisades High (Melana Luke, Karen Beard, Louise Fusfeld, Sherrill Kahn, Dayna Adams, and April Cline), 4/10/78
    - 4/13/78
      - Kim Bower, Republican page
      - Brian Lee, Explorer Scout and Kim Krause, friend
    - President Carter, 4/15/78
    - 4/17/78
      - President Carter
      - President Carter, Admiral Rickover, Zbigniew Brzezinski
    - 4/20/78
      - "Business Roundtable" Malcolm Lovell, Jr., Richard Schubert, William Kolberg, Lewis Foy
      - Lewis Foy, Chairman of Bethlehem Steel Corporation
      - Tim Leighton, intern
      - James Bloom, Morgan Graschel
      - Basil Williams III, John Greenwalt, Ted Higgins, Howard March, Michael Golub, students
    - Brian Hooker, Page and Tom Murphy, intern, 4/24/78
    - Secretarial staff (list attached), 4/27/78
    - 5/2/78
      - SF County Supervisor Quentin Kopp
      - SF Chamber of Commerce
    - 5/4/78
      - Intern Mike Bendorf
      - Intern Debbie Kanarek
      - Intern Doug Tom
    - Intern Ernie Riffenburgh, 5/9/78
    - 5/10/78
      - Staff aid Glenn Rochkind
      - MS Society Father of the Year, Dr. Phillip Itkoff
    - 5/16/78
      - Intern Alan Forst
      - Dellums' page Anthony Thompson
    - Gene Prat, Jack Goldberger, Secretary-Treasurer, Newspaper and Periodical Drivers and Helpers, 5/17/78
    - Tilman O'Bryant, staff assistant, Urban Affiars, 6/9/78
    - Lyle Meek family, 6/13/78
    - Rod Pulley, Executive Director, Housing Authority of Santa Cruz, 6/15/78
    - 6/26/78
      - Alfago Clark, staff aid
      - Blair Tyler, Trudy Powers' friend
    - Frank Hill, Mr. and Mrs. Bob Naylor, Gene Prat, 6/27/78
    - SIH at Stockton Waterloo Activity, 7/5/78
    - Mr. and Mrs. Nathan Levy, 7/12/78
    - Senators Long and Matsunaga w/Japanese Diet headed by Chairman Shiro Nakano, 7/13/78
    - Waler Raheb, 7/16/78
    - 7/17/78
      - Richard Rashman, CA Republican League
      - Geoffrey Gibbs, Gary De Pew, Tom Moore - Boys Nation
    - Senators Heinz & Garn, Bishop Abel Muzorewa and aides, 7/18/78
    - 7/19/78
      - Dayna Carrall and two Swedish exchange students
      - Yvonne Fink, 4H citizenship
      - Anne Moore's sister, Jane Halliburton
    - 7/24/78
      - Francis Troppe, Steve McCormick, Patrick Jewell
      - Meredith, Lauren Preston and Kay Merrill
      - CA Social Studies Teachers Patricia Flaherty, Pamela O'Brien, Shelly Hawkeswood
    - 7/25/78
      - Intern Doug Lee
      - Intern Ben Haddad
      - Intern Richard Flannery
      - Intern Arsen Malkasian
      - Jill Elisofon, Mark Bronson, Lee Bronson, Mrs. Smith for Bronson Collection - Zaire Art/African Art Musieum
      - Mrs. Mitzo Tsujimoto and daughter
    - San Diego Councilman Bill Lowery, George Gordon, Bill Harrington, 7/27/78
    - 7/28/78
      - Intern Karen Davis
      - Summer interns
    - 8/4/78
      - Intern Nancy Friedman
      - Wallace Campbell of CARE (friend of SIH)
      - James Ware, Republican candidate for Controller
      - Intern Tammy Thompson
      - Inter Drew Fransen
      - Intern Graham Walker
    - A. L. Buffington, President, Diamond/Sunsweet, Inc., 8/7/78
    - 8/9/78
      - Ronald K. Okejire, JACL/So. CA Representative
      - Intern Baird Straughan
    - 8/10/78
      - Intern David Ritchie
      - Staff aid Terry Hinch
      - House page Petina Kaplan
      - Intern Melinda Wolfe
    - 8/11/78
      - L.A. Judge Ricks
      - Intern Tim Bobbitt
      - Intern Karen Hirayama
      - Richard Flannery, parents, sister and aunt
      - Fred Ryan, Congressman Dornan's office
    - Dr. Earl Jones, (VP/SF State) and family, 8/14/78
    - 8/16/78 (Box 239)
      - Mr. & Mrs. T. W. Anderson and family
      - Chery Ann Wong
      - Anne Moore's in-laws, Mr. & Mrs. Hubert Moore
    - 8/18/78
      - Intern Kevin Keane
      - Republican Conference
      - Intern Susan Cole
    - 8/21/78
      - Gene Prat
      - Page Michael Montgomery
    - Intern Dan Ichinaga, 8/24/78
    - Staff aide Ronnie Doherty and parents, 8/26/78
    - Constituent Diana Feldman; scuba diving at San Diego Sea World, 8/78
    - NFIB President Wilson Johnson, 9/13/78
    - Gerald R. Ford, International Investors Forum, 9/16/78
    - President Carter, P.M. Begin, President Sadat, 9/18/78
    - 9/19/78
      - President Sadat
      - Gordana Swanson, Mayor Pro-tem, Rolling Hills, CA
      - President Sadat
    - United Youth Society - Daniel Schultz, Kenny Baker, Manny Perez, Salvador Ruiz, Bobby Lays, Steve Content, Richard Susman, Brad Parish, 9/25/78
    - Rhodesian press conference, Fall 1978
    - SIH interview, 10/5/78
    - 10/9/78
      - Prime Minister Ian Smith, Reverend Sithole
      - Senator Garn meeting w/Prime Minister Ian Smith
      - Senator Goldwater, Prime Minister Ian Smith
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Reverend Sithole at press conference
    - 10/10/78
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Reverend Sithole, Senator Goldwater
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Reverend Sithole, Senators Weicker and Garn
      - Senator Heinz and P.M. Ian Smith
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Senators Garn and Chafee
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Reverend Sithole
      - Senator Wallop and Reverend Sithole
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Senator Wallop
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Senator Sparkman, Reverend Sithole
      - P.M. Ian Smith, Reverend Sithole en route to L.A.
    - Latin Businessmen's Association, L.A., CA, 10/27/78
    - 1/79
      - State Senator William Campbell
      - Republican 96th Senatorial Congress
    - 1/16/79
      - Susan Alvarado
      - Barbara Andrews
    - 1/18/79
      - Linda Manske, staff
      - Gene Prat and Linda Manske, staff
      - Jeff Marston, staff (2 photos)
    - 1/19/79
      - Senators Hayakawa and Stevens with Jeff Marston and Wayne Schley
      - SIH w/Senator Stevens and Gene Prat
      - Students from Serra Padre H.S.
    - Joint Session of Congress, 1/23/79
    - Ruby Smith, 1/25/79
    - Travers City, Michigan, 1/26/79
    - Luncheon for Chinese Delegation, 1/30/79
    - Small Business Committee hearings, 2/1/79
    - Ingrid Avedo and Helen Schvenka, 2/2/79
    - CA Avocado Growers, 2/9/79
    - Far West Ski Association, 2/12/79
    - CA Congressmen - Grisham, Matsui, Thomas Dannemeyer, Fazio, 3/8/79
    - CA interns from UCLA, 3/9/79
    - Senators Jepsen and Durenberger, 3/12/79
    - Dr. Garrity, President Central Washington University, 3/13/79
    - Dunn Valdez, 3/14/79
    - Carried Friend and Steve Kelmar, staff, 3/21/79
    - 4/4/79 (Box 240)
      - California School Officials Russell Mathews, Tim Williams, Stanley Won
      - Explorer Scouts George Wagenseller, Anthony Newcomb, Sam Arroyo, Paul Harrison, Barry Hoiser
    - Red Skelton and Gene Prat, 4/6/79
    - Mr. & Mrs. Joseph Wineroth and family, 4/9/79
    - 4/10/79
      - Students of Rancho Palos Verdes, Miralista H.S.
      - 6 Newport Harbor H.S. students
      - 8 Whittier H.S. students
      - Vallecito School, San Rafael, CA students
      - Freedom Foundation member of Santa Ana
    - 4/11/79
      - June Taylor, staff
      - Senator Thurmond and Duncan Howard family
    - Mr. & Mrs. Roos, 4/12/79
    - 4/24/79
      - Todd Dreadgill
      - Rabii Judah Glasner
      - Israel Rosales
    - S.F. Chamber of Commerce, 4/30/79
    - 5/1/79
      - Chuck Yob and Hank Fuhs
      - Bill Combs, Mayor of Moraga and Richard Scott, President CA Chamber
    - 5/5/79
      - Central Washington University
      - Bret Weiss
    - 5/8/79
      - Paul Shimada staff
      - Carrie McCauley
      - Leitkia Chen
      - Jeannine Saunders
      - Chrissie Sacino
    - 5/14/79
      - Mayor Kleiner of Lancaster and Councilmen, member of Board of Trade from Lancaster, CA
      - Patricia Parks, Laurie Baker, Gene Prat
    - Jewish Federation Council Community Relations Committee, 5/17/79
    - 6/5/79
      - Intern Mark Perkins
      - Intern Carol Sarian
      - Mr. & Mrs. Knapp, Margaret Reihlmann, and Danny Murray
      - Intern Chuck Barson
      - Dr. Larry Murphy, Arlington, VA
      - Francine Malone, staff, brother Garrett
      - Gene Prat, Barb Bacci, staff
    - Senate pages, 6/6/79
    - 6/12/79
      - Senate page
      - NFIB
    - Mr. & Mrs. Hunter Land, 6/15/79
    - 6/18/79
      - Joanne McCollough
      - Laura Jettson
      - Phil Proulx
      - Jim Blackwood, staff
      - Tom Burlich
      - Mike Burliss
    - Mr. & Mrs. Brown and Sally Brown, 6/20/79
    - Dr. Christian Barnard, 6/27/79
    - Schlemesons, 7/10/79
    - The Fletchers, 7/11/79
    - Keith Coplen, Gene Prat, Laurie Baker, 7/23/79
    - 7/27/79
      - The Bellwethers of Garden Grove
      - Gene Prat, Keith Coplen from Burbank
      - Alex Kwon, intern
      - Intern Rico Gonzales
      - Intern Missy Moore
      - Intern Charlie Petritis
      - Intern Megan Welsh
      - Inter Cally Sutter
    - 7/30/79
      - Senate pages
      - Father Burbank
    - 8/1/79
      - Intern Ellen McKissock
      - Anne Moore and Ellen McKissock
    - 9/25/79
      - Intern Cathryne Bray
      - Weicker page
      - Intern Janet Fekete
      - Intern Brian Kidney
      - Ted Cramer
      - Anne Moore, staff
      - Suzanne Ploughman, staff
      - Intern Lauren Wander
      - Dennis Parobek (staff) and wife
      - Carla and Chris Vohelpohl
    - Black Businessmen's Association from L.A., 9/27/79
    - 9/28/79
      - Members of National Restaurant Association
      - Ted Balesteri and Robert Power
      - National Restaurant Association
    - Author Joseph Wambaugh, 10/18/79
    - 10/24/79
      - John Kresse, staff
      - Intern Hugh Orosco
      - Jerry Partane, staff
      - Don Galbraith
    - Steve and Brian Kelmar, staff, 11/2/79
    - Linda Jenks, staff, and family, 11/5/79
    - 11/16/79
      - National Conference of Negro Women
      - The Kelmars
      - David Jenks (intern)
      - Joseph Scott and Bob Bush
      - Claudia Conroy, staff
      - Intern Stephanie Prince (2 photographs)
      - Intern Suzanne Woods
    - Don Walsh of USC Institute of Oceanography, 11/19/79
    - 11/26/79
      - The Louie Vanduzers
      - Sandra Smoley, County Supervisor, 3rd District, Sacramento
    - 11/27/79
      - Senator Cranston, Judge Hufstedler, Secretary Department of Education
      - Gloria Blum, constituent
      - Grace Hussie, staff
    - Al Rose, 11/28/79
    - 11/29/79
      - Page Mark Hitchcock
      - Page Mark Russo
      - The Nebekers
      - Interns David Jenks and Suzanne Woods
      - Barb Bacci, staff
      - Intern Dennis Parobek
      - Peggy Haberstroh, staff
      - Intern Diane Van Hammor
      - Intern Gigi Dufort
      - Intern Tom Schwartz
      - Carol Gambrel
    - Howard Bobren, Jim Tishler, 11/30/79
    - 12/13/79 (Box 241)
      - Liz Nord
      - Tom Cort
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1/80
    - Prime Minister Thatcher, 1/17/80
    - Senator Heinz re: Pittsburgh Super Bowl victory, 1/24/80
    - 1/25/80
      - Intern Lynn Sonntag
      - Intern John Gordon (2 photographs)
      - Intern Missy Benson (2 photographs)
      - Intern Lisa Scott
      - Intern Lisa Friehl (2 photographs)
      - Intern Gail Nunn (2 photographs)
      - Anne Moore and Lynn Sonntag
      - Intern Jeff Buncke
      - Intern Lance McLean
      - Mayor Corica of Alameda (2 photographs)
      - Intern Lisa Nicholas (2 photographs)
      - Intern Blake Brydon (2 photographs)
      - Intern Lance McLean
    - Members of Assn. of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1/31/80
    - Steven Gamble and son Dana, 2/5/80
    - 2/6/80
      - Hearst Youth Foundation delegates
      - Francine Malone
      - CA State Student Assn.
    - Senator Wallop, 2/8/80
    - Judge Rolph, Mr. Downer, 2/20/80
    - President of Kenya, 2/21/80
    - Haberstroh family, 2/22/80
    - 2/27/80
      - President Saxon of U. CA system
      - Young Jewish leaders of United Jewish Appeal
    - Volunteer Roland Springborn, 3/13/80
    - Jewish Federation of L.A., 3/19/80
    - Lumber Merchants Assn., 3/20/80
    - Mayor Kathie Wright, Councilman Gallegly, City Manager Lin Koester, 3/26/80
    - 3/27/80
      - Mystery H.S.
      - Members CA School Boards
    - 3/28/80
      - SIH in constituent T-shirt
      - Tippi Hedren
      - Matthew Eagleson
    - Mr. Godi and CA Assn of Realtors, 4/1/80
    - 4/2/80
      - Newport Harbor H.S.
      - Steve Brummel and Mr. & Mrs. Bourriague
    - 4/15/80
      - Attorney General Deukmejian
      - Assn. Builders and Contractors
    - 4/22/80
      - Big Sur Group
      - Reception for SIH's mother
      - Dr. & Mrs. Bjonerud
      - New Covenant Christian H.S. of Palo Alto
    - 4/23/80
      - CA Ag. Leadership lunch (2 photographs)
      - John Crossland
      - San Diego Chamber of Commerce
    - 4/28/80
      - Assemblyman Bruce Young
      - Laurie Baker, Gene Prat, Barb Bacci
    - 4/29/80
      - Meadow Oaks School from Calabasas
      - L.A. Bar Assn.
      - David Anderson, William Griffith, of GTE
      - Staff and interns
    - The Parks, Patty White, 4/30/80
    - Members Sacramento Chamber of Commerce, 5/5/80
    - W. Chambers, Sr. Intern, 5/8/80
    - SIH mother, 5/12/80
    - 5/13/80
      - Colonel Little John of Herlon, CA 13
      - Mike Scavo from Lone Pine
    - 5/14/80
      - Steve Rinehart, attorney
      - Dan O'Hara
    - Sr. Interns from CA, 5/15/80
    - Senior Citizens from Oakland, 5/16/80
    - 5/20/80
      - Tom Curtis, Bruce Curtis, Andrew Marin
      - Jack Brewer
    - 6/5/80 (Box 242)
      - Birgit Noh from Germany
      - Summer helper John Stinmetz
      - Janice Englehart, Patrick Ryan, pages
      - The Loquaci's
      - Page John Gordon and mother
      - Juvenile Diabetes group
      - Chris and Larry Groves, staff
      - Intern Charles Huckelberry, Congresman Panetta
    - 6/13/80
      - Potomac Boat Club
      - Harriet Bell, Thurmond page
      - Liberians
    - 6/17/80
      - Melissa Schukler, and mother
      - Mrs. Sebastiani
    - Members CA Washington Workshop, 6/18/80
    - 6/19/80
      - Duncan Hunter
      - Senator Hatch Intern Ken Wallentine
    - 6/20/80
      - Mary Goedde and friends
      - Ambassador Okawara of Japan
    - 6/23/80
      - Quynh Thai, our page
      - Edith Jones, SIH volunteer in S. D.
    - 6/24/80
      - Dr. Guerra
      - Wilfred Simendinger
      - Cecil Green
      - Bob White
      - Bill Kennedy
      - CA Contract Cities Assn.
      - David Metcalf
      - Councilwoman Faye Dunlap and husband
      - Roy Paul
      - Carol Tanaka, William McCann
      - Mike Montgomery
    - Don Schafer, 6/25/80
    - Paul Fadelli and family, 6/26/80
    - 6/27/80
      - Todd Glanz, intern
      - Intern Robert Kwong
      - Intern Alan Nichols
      - Marikay Shaw
      - George Brazier
      - Rick Schwabacher
      - Intern Erin Wright
      - Intern Kathy Mullen
      - Intern Mary Avshagouni
      - Marian Hopkins and family